

# **HAO NGO**

# FRONT-END

# PERSONAL INFORMATION

DOB: 15 Jan 2000

Gender: Male

Phone: 0944334052

Email: ngotrieuhao@gmail.com Address: District 8, Ho Chi Minh

City

Github: github.com/ngotrieuhao

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/h%E1%BA%A3o-

ng%C3%B4-795998184/

Website:

https://ngotrieuhao.github.io/portfo

liohtmljs/

# **OBJECTIVE**

Apply the knowledge learned in school and self-study about building a website to experience in a dynamic and professional environment. From there, develop professional skills, learn new programming knowledge to successfully complete the assigned work.

#### **SKILLS**

- Hard skill
  - HTML
  - CSS
  - Javascript

#### Soft skill

- Teamwork
- Self-Study
- Problem-Solving

# **EDUCATION**

Major: Information Technology

# **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

2021/06 - 2021/12

**E-commerce Website (Shoes Store)** 

Role: Front-End Developer

Teamsize: 4
Responsibilities:

- Plan ideas and sketch out diagram
- Write website code with programming languages such as: HTML, CSS and Javascript
- Fix any website issues or bugs that arise
- Turn UI/UX designs into prototypes, create excellent interactions from designs Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Boostrap

2021/01 - 2021/04

**Student Management Website** 

Role: Front-End Developer

Teamsize: 6
Responsibilities:

- Write website code with programming languages such as HTML, CSS and Javascript
- Turn UI/UX designs into prototypes, create excellent interactions from designs

Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap

### **ACTIVITY**

2019-2020 Join the Hackathon contest